<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2017-05-27T22:49:28+03:00</updated><id>localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Reinards</title><subtitle>See my amazing portfolio. It might not have that much content for now, but it will change.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Our first game</title><link href="localhost:4000/jekyll/game/programming/2017/05/25/our-first-game.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our first game" /><published>2017-05-25T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2017-05-25T00:00:00+03:00</updated><id>localhost:4000/jekyll/game/programming/2017/05/25/our-first-game</id><content type="html" xml:base="localhost:4000/jekyll/game/programming/2017/05/25/our-first-game.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Squane is out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The development of this game was inactive for more than a year. But I did it.&lt;br /&gt;
Niks wouldn’t want to participate(kinda), because I used the Godot game engine to rebuild this game.\&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, the rebuild was not good. It had slow performance, it was too easy and repeating.&lt;br /&gt;
After publishing it, there were some recommendations to make this game more difficult, what I did.&lt;br /&gt;
I added mini-map for colors, I made slide-selecting possible, I also improved performance and data saving mechanics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game didn’t get more than 50 downloads, but it was our first game. We have earned 5 cents in total, haha.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My next game will be better. I cannot think of something interesting and fun, but I know the idea will come and as soon as it happens, I will try to realise it, just for fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;If anyone wonders about what is Godot, then I can say it is the best game engine I have found so far!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello again!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to my blog!</title><link href="localhost:4000/jekyll/introduction/2017/03/26/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to my blog!" /><published>2017-03-26T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-03-26T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>localhost:4000/jekyll/introduction/2017/03/26/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="localhost:4000/jekyll/introduction/2017/03/26/first-post.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I am 17 years old boy from Latvia. I have been interested in programming since 2012.&lt;br /&gt;
My friend Niks, was already learning programming for one year when he tried to convince me to try it too.
I started with competitive programming - the only thing I was/am taught by that teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have always been interested in learning things that are useful in the real life. I cannot remember when it happened, but the same friend who interested me in competitive programming taught me a little bit of html and css.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I can still remember that green website which used Javascript to toggle a div :D&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That spark started a fire in me. From then, more or less, I have been learning html, css, javascript and many other programming things.&lt;br /&gt;
Each year there was a programmers camp in which we were taught different technologies. PHP was a very cool one.
After that one camp I had an intention to make a world-changing website… like Facebook.&lt;br /&gt;
Of course, I didn’t make anything big. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the last one year I have been interested even more.&lt;br /&gt;
I have learned to use SASS (It is so much easier to write css now).&lt;br /&gt;
I have learned to make simple websites with Django and Jekyll (This website is powered by Jekyll :P)&lt;br /&gt;
I have discovered many awesome frameworks and libraries.&lt;br /&gt;
I have learned a bunch of stuff. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made this website because I feel the need for a place where I can express my thoughts and show off my work.&lt;br /&gt;
In a nutshell, I will make a post whenever I have something cool to say to you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you did read this far, great! But this blog will not only contain posts related to programming. I also like to paint with watercolors, pencil and black pens. I am experimenting with songwriting(It is way harder than I thought it would be). You can expect all kinds of different posts here.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;So, stay tuned and have a nice day!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome!</summary></entry></feed>